

Le Thi Ngoc Tram

CONTACT INFORMATION

- **May 18, 1995**
- Female
- **** 037 7080465
- Quynhtram1995ydh@gmail.com
- P Hatinh, Vietnam
- https://www.facebook.com/LeNgocTram

OBJECTIVE

I am seeking job that provides an opportunity to take advantage of English, computer, independent and teamwork skills. From that, I will contribute to the development of Company.

Five-year goal: Become a teamleader and lead the team to become a cadre of the company.

SKILLS

Microsoft office

Independent

Teamwork

Reseacher

English

Comminucation

INTERESTS

Read books

Listen to music

Do yoga

EDUCATION

Sep 2013 - May 2018

HUE UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY

Major: Pharmacy

- GPA: 7.9
- Certificate in Applied Informatics Technology
- TOEIC 895

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct 2017 - May 2018

DEFEND THE THESIS ON A TOPIC "RESEARCH GEL COVERING PHYTOSOME QUERCETIN"

Carrying out the research and completing the topic under the guidance of university professors.

Feb 2018 - Apr 2018

MEDIPARCO- TENAMYD CENTRAL PHARMACEUTICAL JOINT STOCK COMPANY AND HUE UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL

Main responsibilities:

- Observe and report the medicine production and store line
- Evaluate the doctors prescriptions Achievements and Gains:
- Get knowledge of GPs
- Understand the roles of pharmacist in pharmaceutical companies and hospitals

Apr 2018 - Apr 2018

GOOD PHARMACY NO.2

Medicine seller

Main responsibilities:

- Study clinical knowledge
- Consult customers and sell medicine

Achievements and skills gained:

- Obtain clinical knowledge of common diseases and drugs
- Improve the consultancy skills

Feb 2014 - Jun 2014

TUTOR

Mathematics and English language Tutor Main responsibilities:

- Compose lesson plans and explain it easily to my student

Achievements and skills gained:

- Improve the communication skills
- Support my student to understand the essence of problems and get excellent mark.

REFERENCES

Nguyen Hong Trang

Professor of Hue university of medicine and pharmacy

Email: hongtrang1604@gmail.com

Mobile: 091 2325695.

ACTIVITIES

2013 - 2017

Participating in music program in my class

- Dancing and singing activities on special events.

Jan 2016 - May 2016

Participating in the activities team of Hue teenagers

- Organizing charity activities for children in Hue Central Hospital
- Improving teamwork ability to handle my daily life